greatcollections.com 2019-04-28

# GreatCollections - Privacy

Updated February 12, 2011

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

\- To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

\- To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

\- To send periodic e-mails. The e-mail address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future e-mails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each e-mail.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**

We use cookies as a means for our technology to identify return clients, in a similar way to how Amazon.com, eBay.com and Google.com use cookies. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third-party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Therefore, we will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

 **Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act); we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy.

 **Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on February 12, 2011.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below. 

**Great** Collections.com, LLC.  
17500 Red Hill Avenue, Suite 160,  
Irvine, CA 92614  
United States  
E-mail: [[email protected]](https://www.greatcollections.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#83eaede5ecc3e4f1e6e2f7e0ecefefe6e0f7eaecedf0ade0ecee)  
Tel: +1-949-679-4180  
Fax: +1-949-679-4178
